var data = [
  {
    category: "React 101",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "What tool Creates a React app with no build configuration?",
        options: [
          "A. create-react-build",
          "B. create-react-app",
          "C. create-react",
          "D. All of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "B. create-react-app"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "What type of react component can maintain state?",
        options: [
          "A. Functional Component",
          "B. Logical Component",
          "C. Stateful Component",
          "D. Class Component"
        ],
        answer: "D. Class Component"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What does JSX stand for?",
        options: [
          "A. JavaScript XML",
          "B. JavaScript eXchange",
          "C. JavaScipt Shorthand SyntaX",
          "D. JavaScript SyntaX (10)"
        ],
        answer: "A. JavaScript XML"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question: "Which example would be invalid JSX?",
        options: [
          "A. <div className=\"Button\" />",
          "B. <div id=\"Button\" />",
          "C. <div class=\"Button\" />",
          "D. All of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "C. <div class=\"Button\" />"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category: "JavaScript",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "What are ways of handling Asynchronous Code?",
        options: [
          "A. callbacks, returns, promises",
          "B. async/await, callbacks, returns",
          "C. callbacks, async/await, promises",
          "D. returns, try/catch, closures"
        ],
        answer: "C. callbacks, async/await, promises"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "What are 3 ways to define a variable in JavaScript?",
        options: [
          "A. set, var, let",
          "B. let, const, set",
          "C. let, value, const",
          "D. var, const, let"
        ],
        answer: "D. var, const, let"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What do three equal signs (===) provide over two equal signs (==)",
        options: [
          "A. Optimal Equality",
          "B. Strict Equality",
          "C. Not a valid syntax",
          "D. Used for Comparing Objects"
        ],
        answer: "B. Strict Equality"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question: "<What is the case convention used in JavaScript?",
        options: [
          "A. snake_case",
          "B. kebab-case",
          "C. camelCase",
          "D. CapitalCase"
        ],
        answer: "C. camelCase"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category: "React 201",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "Which company created React?",
        options: [
          "A. Google",
          "B. Facebook",
          "C. Amazon",
          "D. Oracle"
        ],
        answer: "B. Facebook"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "What part of your application does React focus on?",
        options: [
          "A. The Model",
          "B. The View",
          "C. The Controller",
          "D. All of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "B. The View"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What is a competing front-end framework to React?",
        options: [
          "A. JQuery",
          "B. Express",
          "C. Angular",
          "D. Vanilla JavaScript"
        ],
        answer: "C. Angular"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question: "How is data passed down from one React component to another?",
        options: [
          "A. props",
          "B. attributes",
          "C. classes and id's",
          "D. All of the Above"
        ],
        answer: "A. props"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    category: "General",
    questions: [
      {
        points: 100,
        question: "What does DOM stand for?",
        options: [
          "A. Data Object Model",
          "B. Document Object Model",
          "C. Dynamic Object Model",
          "D. Domain Object Medium"
        ],
        answer: "B. Document Object Model"
      },
      {
        points: 200,
        question: "Where does the DOM exist?",
        options: [
          "A. The Matrix",
          "B. iOS or Android App",
          "C. The Browser",
          "D. The JavaScript Engine"
        ],
        answer: "C. The Browser"
      },
      {
        points: 300,
        question: "What is SQL?",
        options: [
          "A. Structured Query Language",
          "B. System Query Language",
          "C. Structured Query Learning",
          "D. System Query Level"
        ],
        answer: "A. Structured Query Language"
      },
      {
        points: 400,
        question: "What feature defines a pure function?",
        options: [
          "A. No side effects",
          "B. No return values",
          "C. Always returns the same result for same argument values",
          "D. A and C"
        ],
        answer: "D. A and C"
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default data;
